yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
You have a fever
你发烧了
lie
躺
I will be right back
我马上回来
have a good rest
好好休息
I woke up
我醒了
OK
好的
It's time for breakfast
吃早餐的时间到了
sit
坐
eat quickly
快点吃
sorry
对不起
Mr. Zhang will not leave us
张先生不会离开我们
what should we do
我们应该做什么
Let's surrender
我们去投降吧
if you decide
如果你决定
I will go with you
我和你一起去
Are you awake yet?
你还没醒吗？
I woke up
我醒了
whatever your choice
无论你的选择如何
I will face it with you
我会和你一起面对
when i am abroad
当我在国外的时候
I should have been in jail
我本应该进监狱的
We are just a few years late
我们只是晚了几年
Are you afraid of going to jail?
你害怕坐牢吗？
Who is not afraid
谁不害怕
Do you regret it now?
你现在后悔了吗？
when you come back to me
当你回来找我的时候
And you?
你呢？
Do you regret knowing me?
你后悔认识我吗？
Zisheng
子升
Yaw Yaw is
偏航 偏航 是
Don't apologize to me again
不要再向我道歉
I have
我有
for me
为我
we are done
我们完成了
No one owes anyone
没有人欠任何人的
I don't want to go to jail
我不想进监狱
I don't want you to go to jail
我不想让你进监狱
so don't worry
所以不用担心
we absolutely are
我们绝对是
Looking for ways to save ourselves
寻找拯救我们自己的方法
but they are
但他们是
they won't let us leave
他们不会让我们离开
This is Tianhai
这里是天海
They won't do what they want to do
他们不会做他们想做的事
Should we?
我们应该吗？
Continue the mission?
继续执行任务？
there is nothing
没有什么
Other tests
其他检查
Don't worry
不用担心
It’s not easy to enter a state-owned enterprise
进国企不容易
we will wait for the opportunity
我们会等待机会
let's eat
我们吃饭吧
until I'm satisfied
直到我满意之后
Except after meals
除了饭后
like this
就像这样
I'll go to the planning office to check
我去规划办公室查看
at the beginning
在一开始的时候
that hotel
那家酒店
Call for the construction of signal towers
要求修建信号塔
The person in charge of approval is Sun
负责审批的人是孙
he admits
他承认
He took Zhao Jun's money
他拿了赵军的钱
and help him secretly
并且暗中帮助他
After approval
批准后
If you say this Zhao Jun
如果你说这个赵军
I knew it wasn't built
我就知道它没有建成
He must know
他一定知道
So it came true
于是它也成真了
Zhaojun Company
兆骏公司
He and Chen Tingyunyi
他和陈庭韵伊
In the past few years
在过去的几年里
so
所以
relationship between them
他们之间的关系
no coincidence
并非巧合
Where is Zhao Jun now?
赵军现在在哪里？
Business trip to nearby cities
邻近城市出差
we can't wait
我们等不及了
Go to the next city to find Zhao Jun
前往下一个城市寻找赵军
this is very important
这是非常重要的
penetration
渗透
also
此外
Chen Ting's place
陈婷的地方
Then it
那它
in the human relationship picture
在人际关系图画中
I sent someone to monitor him
我派人去监视他
Then go quickly
那就快点走吧
OK
好的
How is the situation now?
现在情况怎么样？
Looking for people at the top
寻找高层的人
To alleviate this problem
为了缓解这个问题
it means i can come back
这意味着我可以回来
really
确实
before you come back
在你回来之前
i will teach you how
我会教你如何
How to explain this story
怎么解释这个故事
If the national security comes to find you again
如果国安再找你
you will know
你会知道
how to deal with them
如何对付他们
OK
好的
Where did we meet?
我们哪见
therefore
因此
Wait for my message later
稍后等我的消息
OK
好的
Dai Wei 6 7 8
戴伟 6 7 8
But they just asked me
但他们只是问我
Is the car mine?
车是我的吗？
We need to deliver the gun
我们要把枪送到
No. 9772 Olympic Street
奥林匹克街9772号
This is the address
这是地址
how's it going
怎么样了
half time every day
每天一半时间
Looking for the right person for you
正在寻找适合你的人
do you accept it
你接受了吗
Behind me?
在我后面儿？
I won't let you do it in vain
我不会让你白干
one hundred gold coins
一百金币
Don't you have money?
你没钱吗？
I sold all my first gear.
我卖掉了所有的第一件装备
Is it worth some money?
值得一些钱吗
So I'll shoot you now
所以我现在就开枪打死你
Can't you resist?
你就不能反抗吗？
What's your job?
你做什么工作？
Photography Featured Workers
拍摄特色工人
I can upgrade several levels in a row
我可以连续升级几个等级
then you
然后你
Can you tell me?
你能告诉我吗？
Before the shoot?
拍摄前？
I checked it for you
我帮你查了一下
she deleted her account
她删除了她的帐户
I left the game
我离开了游戏
I found you...
我发现你...
After meeting your partner in the game
在游戏中遇见你的伙伴后
a lot of bad things happened
发生了很多不好的事情
You are the truth again
你又是真理了
but not all
但不是所有的
man
男人
Can you help me search it?
你能帮我搜索一下吗？
Clear task log
清除任务日志
before game
比赛前
she lost her account
她失去了账户
Where can I find you?
我可以去哪里找你？
I can help you find this
我可以帮你找到这个
all is well
一切都很好
this is correct
这是对的
Register for a virtual world
注册一个虚拟世界
can delete
可以删除
Memories in real life cannot be deleted
现实生活中的记忆是无法删除的
i won't thank you
我不会感谢你
Do you want to escape?
你想逃跑吗？
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
No
不
Do you really want to shoot me?
你真的要开枪打我吗？
There is no equipment here
这里没有设备
you will be bullied
你会被欺负
take it
拿去
I have been preparing for a long time
我已经准备了很久
will be open tomorrow
明天将开放
i hope you are encouraged
我希望你受到鼓励
art forever
艺术永
Mrs. Chen, are you finished?
陈太太，你说完了吗？
I'm back
我回来了
Have you eaten yet?
你吃过了吗？
No
不
let's go together
咱们一起去吧
OK
好的
Why are you at home at this time?
你怎么这个时候在家？
I'm going to visit this afternoon
我今天下午去拜访
You came back to change clothes
你回来换衣服了
Why are you back too?
怎么你也回来了？
Is there anything
有没有什么
there is nothing
没有什么
I just passed by
我刚刚路过
I'll go back and get some things
我回去拿一些东西
I heard about your art museum
听说你们的美术馆
will be open tomorrow
明天将开放
Did Brother Cheng tell you?
程哥告诉你了吗？
I think you are
我想你是
tell your family
告诉你的家人
I won't say it anyway
反正我不会说
Someone will also tell you
也会有人告诉你
tomorrow
明天
in free time
在空闲时
Me and your mother
我和你妈妈
and your mother
和你妈妈
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
when i'm happy
当我高兴的时候
I must cooperate with you
我必须和你合作
Represents the Family Peace series, right?
代表家庭和平系列吧？
Pay attention to your tone
注意你的语气
What's wrong with me?
我怎么了？
What's wrong
怎么了
You are wrong
您错了
sorry
对不起
i know what to say
我知道该说什么
Welcome, Mayor Fang
欢迎您，方市长
Mayor Fang
方市长
he comes to visit
他来拜访
Opened his own art museum
开设了自己的美术馆
perhaps
或许
you bastard
你这个混蛋
if
如果
Did you quarrel again?
你们又吵架了吗？
speak calmly
平静地说话
Do you have time on the weekend?
周末你有时间吗？
Then let's talk
那我们来谈谈吧
welcome
欢迎
I want to ask
我想问一下
Do you have
有没有
Is there a person named Zhao Jun?
有一个人叫赵军吗？
His name is Zhao Jun
他的名字叫赵军
Zhao Junyou
赵军右
Let me check it for you
我帮你查一下
Okay, thank you
好，谢谢
Tian Yang
田阳
Zhao Jun is in the underground car warehouse
赵军在地下汽车仓库里
I gotta go
我要走了
Should I stop him?
我应该阻止他吗？
No need to follow it first
无需先遵循它
OK
好的
Why did you change your number?
你为什么改变号码？
Safety
安全
What happened?
发生了什么事吗？
Let's talk when we meet
见面时我们聊聊
Where
在哪里
Visayas
米沙湾
fully understand
完全了解
Please go this way, Mayor Fang
请这边走，方市长
OK
好的
thank you today
今天谢谢你
To take up your valuable time
为了占用您的宝贵时间
Go to data center
前往数据中心
I've wanted this place for a long time
我想这个地方很久了
take a look
看一看
from here
从这里
OK
好的
Help yourself
帮助自己
Mayor Fang
方市长
look left
向左看
this class
这个班
This is our intellectual reading
这是我们的智力阅读
in data center
在数据中心
we depend on
我们依赖
Xiaoyu Lake
小鱼湖
lower their temperature
降低它们的温度
Because of the temperature of the lake water
因为湖水的温度
relatively low
相对较低
After scanning
扫描后
flow per layer
每层流动
to lower their body temperature
为了降低他们的体温
We have calculated the first step
我们已经计算了第一步
if you do
如果你这样做
can provide
可以提供
80%
80%
Hope so
希望也是
Quarterly readings will decrease
季度读数会减少
and make their own contribution
并做出自己的贡献
OK
好的
The essence of technology model
技术模式本质
live in city
住在城市里
random communication
随机交流
this is amazing
这真太了不起了
The next step is city government
下一步是市政府
Be ready for next year
明年做好准备
next year
明年
in data center
在数据中心
Yes or no? this is amazing
是不是？这真太了不起了
Please start here
请从这里开始
I'll take you to the computer room
我带你去电脑室
look
看
Mayor Fang
方市长
Anyway
反正
without your support
没有你的支持
we can't
我们不可以
We can't set up a data center
我们无法建立数据中心
in this era
在这个时代
This is the display of your youth
这是你青春的展现
I'm not young anymore
我不年轻了
Mayor Fang, look
方市长你看
It's all under thermostatic control
这一切都在恒温控制下
These are all under the control of numbers
这些都在数字的掌控之中
This is a full crystal display
这是全水晶展示
If you want to control the heat
如果你想控制火候
Everything is under your control
一切尽在您的掌控之中
Can I touch your hand like this?
像这样摸你的手好吗
mayor
市长
noon time
中午时间
I've done it for you
我已经为你完成了
I won't go in the afternoon
下午我不会去
I prepared a gift in the box at the back
我在后面的盒子里准备了一份礼物
at the right time
在适当的时候
bring him
带给他
Tell him congratulations on your opening
告诉他恭喜你开业
Did you give her a gift?
你给她送礼物了吗？
OK
好的
I have invited you
我已经请了你
Well, come in
嗯，进来吧
Welcome to enter
欢迎您进入
welcome
欢迎
I have invited you
我已经请了你
Brother Cheng
程弟兄
Congratulations, Lu
恭喜你，卢
you achieved your dream
你实现了你的梦想
You come alone
你一个人来
The mayor held an extraordinary meeting
市长召开临时会议
I can't get out
我出不去
He is very busy
他很忙
This is for you
这是给您的
opening gift
开业礼物
This is an edit table
这是一个编辑表
Daytona Co. Picasso
代托纳有限公司毕加索
I think you will like it
我想你一定会喜欢它
You shouldn't buy this
你不应该买这个
What?
什么？
If I don't buy it, you don't like it
如果我不买，你就不喜欢
Nothing to do with this
与此无关
if i buy it i will like it
如果我买它我会喜欢它
if he is
如果他是
All right
好吧
take me to see
带我去看
I tell you
我告诉你
don't blame him
别怪他
He has a high status and dignity
他地位高，有尊严
but he
但是他
some things are clear
有些事情很清楚
He doesn't like to express
他不喜欢表达
In fact, he cares about you very much
其实他很在乎你
look
看
This watch I chose for you
我为你挑选的这款手表
I chose it for you
我为你选择的
The nature of father and son
父亲和儿子的本质
impossible
不可能
it cannot be destroyed
它无法被摧毁
I think he is a normal person
我认为他是一个正常人
Both father and son are righteous
父子俩都是正义的
in the end
到底
Gift
礼物
She invited others to come
她请其他人来
You two are fighting
你们两个在打架
I don't know when
我不知道什么时候
To make it clear
为了说清楚
so can i clarify
所以我可以澄清一下
sometimes i think
有时我想
In fact, you are more
其实你更
More than my family
比我的家人还多
no matter what happens
无论发生什么
You were the one who came before me
你是比我先来的人
help me solve the problem
帮助我解决问题
What about him?
那么他呢？
I obey his orders
我听从他的命令
under any circumstances
任何状况之下
preferably
最好是
for me
为我
I can't give it back to you
我不能把它还给你
If I fail at work I will be reprimanded
如果我工作失败我会受到谴责
Can you bear it?
你能忍受吗？
It’s right to watch my elder brother being scolded
看着大哥被骂对了
my brother, tell the truth
我的兄弟，说实话
He scolded me more than he scolded you.
他骂我比骂你还多
I tell you
我告诉你
I
我
like cake
喜欢蛋糕
I'm really tired
我真的累了
if you want
如果你想要的话
You can return the product yourself
您可以自行退货
Secretary Cheng
程书记
Director Chen
陈主任
they spoke
他们说话了
I want to convey my regards
我想转达我的问候
some friends
一些朋友
OK
好的
how are you my sister
你怎么样我的妹妹
Many people came today
今天来了很多人
it seems
它似乎
everyone supports you
大家都支持你
Actually when I was in school
其实我上学的时候
I like
我喜欢
art museum
美术博物馆
in the museum
在博物馆里
I was thinking
我当时就在想
if you grow up
如果你长大了
i can plan
我可以计划
my gallery
我的画廊
That's great
那太好了
Who would have thought that they would grow up?
谁会想到自己会长大呢？
i dream
我梦想
you didn't expect
你没想到
To succeed in this matter
要想在这件事上取得成功
Yes
是的
now i think about it
现在我想了想
my sisters
我的姐妹
Thanks
谢谢
to realize my dream
为了实现我的梦想
I do not think so
我不这么认为
Senior Technician
高级技工
this is your dream
这是你的梦想
but for me
但对我来说
also
此外
Part of the Yunyi brand
云易品牌的一部分
At least you always support me
至少你一直支持我
look at my father
看看我的父亲
OK
好的
under any circumstances
任何状况之下
i must congratulate you
我必须祝贺你
depends on yourself
取决于你自己
to fulfill your wishes
来满足你的愿望
OK
好的
we don't want to be here
我们不要在这里
high art
高等艺术
Leader of the Cultural Department
文化处领导
they are all there
他们都在那里
I leave it to you
我把它留给你
OK
好的
face the reality
面对现实
Have the ability to go
有能力去
Serving your artistic dreams
服务您的艺术梦想
go
去
how's it going
怎么样了
will end soon
很快就会结束
OK
好的
He has led to places so far away
他曾带领到如此遥远的地方
Strange
奇怪的
a bit strange
有点奇怪
Come and take a look
赶快来看看吧
Are you OK
你好吗
Call an ambulance quickly
赶紧叫救护车
welcome
欢迎
Baishan Road
白山路
There was a car accident
发生了车祸
Yes, two injuries
是的，两处受伤
Hurry up - okay -
快点-好-
on my way
我在途中
Are you OK
你好吗
too late
太晚了
pony
小马
Baishan Road
白山路
something happened
发生了一些事
Welcome to enter
欢迎您进入
Meiyuan Museum
美园博物馆
Yes
是的
this is new
这是新的
welcome
欢迎
this
这
look
看
Do you like modern paintings?
你喜不喜欢现代画？
nature
自然
I am also an artistic man
我也是一个文艺男
I don’t know if you are an artistic man
不知道你是不是文艺男
In any case, he is not an ordinary person
无论如何，他都不是一个普通人
Let's go in and have a look
我们进去看看吧
you
你
Please show your invitation letter
请出示您的邀请函
didn't you
你没有吗
Am I an unreliable person?
我是一个不靠谱的人吗？
Well, come in
嗯，进来吧
Thanks
谢谢
this is a very big
这是一个非常大的
look over there
看那边
here
这里
Yes
是的
Is this it?
这是吗
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
Fang Lu
方璐
What a coincidence
真是巧合
Fang Lu, I saw him last time
方路，我上次见过他
Remember Brother Fang?
还记得方哥吗？
welcome
欢迎
you
你
Why did you come to the art exhibition?
你为什么来看画展？
i saw
我看见
on the Internet
在互联网上
A painter I like very much
我非常喜欢的一个画家
The first exhibition was held in China
首届展会在中国举办
around here today
今天在这附近
I'm here to take a look
我是来看看
I didn't expect it
我原本没想到
I'll take you two shopping
我带你们俩去购物
Is this your quote?
这是你的报价吗？
Yes
是的
Do we make money from this show?
我们靠这个节目赚钱吗？
talk about art
谈论艺术
Artistic young people only talk about art
艺术青年只谈艺术
don't talk about money
不要谈论金钱
I understand, I understand
我明白了，我明白了
no no no
不不不
Mr. Fang
方先生
excuse me
打扰一下
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
Near here
在这附近
There is a Thai restaurant
有一家泰国餐厅
very good
非常好
How about we have dinner together?
我们一起吃晚饭怎么样？
No, we'll do it again tonight
不用了，我们今晚再重复一次
What do you think we should try?
你认为我们应该尝试什么？
your suggestions
您的建议
have fun
玩得开心
I will come to you soon
我很快就会来找你
sorry bro
对不起，兄弟
Sorry to keep you waiting - it's okay -
抱歉让您久等了-没关系-
i met a friend
我遇见了一个朋友
Yes, old colleague
是的，老同事
You made an appointment to have dinner together
你们约好了一起吃晚饭
Then let’s go
那就走吧
I gotta go
我要走了
correct
正确的
in fact
事实上
Grandpa cares about you very much
爷爷很关心你
you can achieve your dreams
你可以实现你的梦想
We are all very happy
我们都很高兴
let's go
我们走吧
Why suddenly?
为什么突然？
very excited
很兴奋
No
不
Who doesn’t eat for free?
谁不吃免费的？
you are not that type
你不是那种类型
He likes to take advantage
他喜欢占便宜
say
说话
what's on your mind?
你在想什么？
I believe
我相信
he is nice to you
他对你很好
What's the relationship between you two?
你们两个是什么关系？
Didn't I tell you before?
我之前不是告诉过你了吗？
we are
我们是
Let's play together
我们一起玩
when we go to school
当我们上学的时候
good friend
好朋友
Why are you nervous?
你为什么紧张？
I'm not nervous
我不紧张
just me
只有我
I don't want to mention it
我不想提
Just talk about the past
只谈过去
past
过去
It has been a long time
已经很久了
there's only us
只有我们
have dinner together
一起吃晚饭
What's more, he and I
更何况，我和他
our relationship is very good
我们的关系很好
you
你
Did something really happen?
难道真的发生了什么事情吗？
childish
幼稚的
I'm kidding
我在开玩笑
If you really don't want to go
如果你实在不想去
I will tell him
我会告诉他
we won't go
我们不去
forget it
忘了它
I agree
我同意
if
如果
in 2009
在2009年
You still have that wooden carousel
你还有那个木制旋转木马
years ago
几年前
from player
来自玩家
in the previous
在之前的
I saw someone selling it online
我看到有人在网上卖
But the price is very high
但价格非常高
I simply can't stand it
我根本无法忍受
I tell you
我告诉你
Actually a few years ago
其实几年前
This product has been copied
该产品已被复制
but little known
却鲜为人知
if you like
如果你喜欢的话
I can help you
我可以帮你
no need
没有必要
Incidentally
顺便一提
I participated in the street series
我参加了街头系列
Rotating Coffee 2007
2007年旋转咖啡
I just received
我刚刚收到
those methods
那些方法
Memories of old times are of great significance
旧时回忆的意义是很大的
but
但
honestly
诚实地
Indoor decorations
室内装饰
needs improvement
需要改进
totally agree
完全同意
in fact
事实上
I'm at home
我在家
at home
在家里
This is the town of Lago
这是拉戈小镇
We're short of regular coffee
我们缺乏普通咖啡
I believe
我相信
if you don't collect
如果你不收集
i feel pain
我感到疼痛
this is power
这就是力量
I envy your real name
我羡慕你的真名
Both of you are modern art
你们两个都是现代艺术
modern art
现代艺术的
not easy
不容易
we can't talk
我们不能说话
snow in spring
春天下雪
our hobbies
我们的爱好
very wide
很宽
That's right, both of you
没错，你们俩
Do you want to drink more?
你想喝更多吗？
i want more wine
我想要更多的酒
not easy to find
不容易找到
have the same ambition
有着同样的野心
perhaps
或许
waiter
服务员
two bottles of beer
两瓶啤酒
Come on, drink this
来吧，喝这个
we drink to you
我们为你干杯
I'm curious
我很好奇
How did you two meet?
你们两个是怎么认识的？
I am playing game
我玩游戏
Are there any games?
有什么游戏吗？
special mission
特殊使命
Is this interesting?
这有趣吗？
There is a pitfall in this game
这游戏有坑
I noticed
我注意到
Not good at playing
玩不好
can easily become dangerous
很容易变得危险
Hello
你好
Understood
明白了
Okay, I'll be right back
好的，我马上回来
What's wrong?
怎么了？
my father forgot the key
我父亲忘记了钥匙
I'll go home and open the door for him
我会回家为他开门
OK, I'll go with you
好的，我和你一起去
No need, no need
不需要，不需要
they keep talking
他们一直在说话
Our house is near here
我们的房子就在这附近
I will be right back
我马上回来
Eat, eat first
吃饭，先吃饭
Still there
还在
play this game
玩这个游戏
sometimes
有时
Something big happened at that time
当时发生了一件大事
don't you think
你不觉得
There is something wrong with this game
这游戏有问题
because there is a problem
因为有问题
so i can move on
所以我可以继续前进
After we go in
我们进去后
Brother Cheng received the news
程哥收到消息
he came here
他来到这里
i am included
我被包括在内
then
当时
I was not in good health at the time
我当时身体不好
as you know
如你所知
you know
你知道
I don't want to get rid of myself
我并不想摆脱自己
After returning to Tianhai
回到天海后
first thing i did
我做的第一件事
He restored my phone
他恢复了我的手机
I will call you
我会打电话给你
But I can't reach you at all
但我根本联系不到你
I sent you an email
我给你发了封邮件
OK
好的
we don't discuss this
我们不讨论这个
it's over
结束了
Do you want me to help you?
你要我帮助你吗？
Have you paid all the money?
你已经付清所有的钱了吗？
I can give it back to you
我可以把它还给你
As long as you don't touch that toy
只要你不碰那个玩具
No need to thank you
不需要谢谢你
i gave everything
我付出了一切
Don't worry
不用担心
I won't play anymore
我不会再玩了
Can we
我们可以吗
Can we become friends
我们能成为朋友吗
in fact
事实上
I was really helpless at that time
当时我真的很无助
Plus a friend left me
再加上一个朋友离开了我
i really hate you
我真的很恨你
But this matter
但此事
It has been a long time
已经很久了
don't mention it
别提它
after that
在那之后
i didn't apologize to you
我没有向你道歉
I formally apologize to you
我正式向你道歉
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
sorry
对不起
Forget about the pain.
痛少就别提了
it's over
结束了
Your boyfriend is very interesting
你男朋友很有趣
we get along very well
我们相处得很好
we are very happy together
我们在一起很开心
No matter what happens
不管发生什么
He won't leave me alone
他不会丢下我一个人
what's on your mind?
你在想什么？
I think of Fang Lu
我想起了方璐
I admit
我承认
I specifically promised him a meal
我特意答应他吃饭
Why
为什么
Deliberate mention of games
故意提到游戏
look
看
after the accident
事故发生后
Spy organizations threaten you
间谍组织威胁你
What about him?
那么他呢？
this is the reason
这就是原因
I don't want to contact him
我不想联系他
Because I do not know
因为我不知道
what happened after
之后发生了什么
Will you face it?
你会面对吗？
Have the same situation as me
和我有同样的情况
this is the reason
这就是原因
I want to talk to him about games
我想和他谈谈游戏
you can tell me directly
你可以直接告诉我
In the end you still don’t believe me
到最后你还是不相信我
No
不
sorry
对不起
I just want to know
我只是想知道
his identity
他的身份
I didn't think too much
我没想太多
What now?
现在呢？
Do you understand it?
你明白了吗？
No
不
All this is because of my father
这一切都是因为我的父亲
call me
打电话给我
after she left
她离开后
What did he tell you?
他告诉你什么了？
he said he
他说他
He won't play games anymore
他不会再玩游戏了
I won't play games anymore
我不会再玩游戏了
Do you think
你认为
Is Fang Lu a spy?
方禄是间谍吗？
I have no idea
我不知道
but i think
但我觉得
At least
至少
about what happened
关于发生的事情
I think so
我也这么认为
Fang Lu
方璐
he seems sincere
他看起来很真诚
It seems not
似乎没有
A person who hides no secrets
一个不隐藏任何秘密的人
how do you know
你怎么知道
intuitive
直觉的
If my intuition helps
如果我的直觉有帮助的话
the two of us
我们两个
we won't be like this
我们不会像现在这样
this is correct
这是对的
right now we
我们现在
we can't protect ourselves
我们无法保护自己
If he partners with Fang Lu
如果他和方璐搭档
With Fang Lu
与方璐
will be more dangerous
会更危险
Whether he has anything to do with it or not
不管他有没有关系
with spies
与间谍
Don't communicate with him
不要和他交流
no longer
不再
OK?
好的？
Zhao Jun suspected that someone
赵军怀疑有人
He is not a target for arrest
他不是逮捕目标
when he follows him
当他追随他的时候
Such an incident occurred
发生了这样的事件
Causes target's death
导致目标死亡
he blames you
他责怪你
Mr. Chen
陈先生
that's too far
那太远了
There are no surveillance cameras on the street
街上没有监控摄像头
But surveillance video shows
但监控视频显示
can prove
可以证明
Mr. Chen, look
陈先生你看
Zhao Jun’s car
赵军的车
He was driving smoothly at that time
当时他开车平稳
But after turning
但转弯后
look
看
The car starts to move left and right
小车开始左右移动
like losing control
就像失去控制一样
when we arrive
当我们到达时
another way
另一种方法
But throughout the process
但在整个过程中
Zhao Jun
赵军
alone in car
独自在车里
Have not communicated
没有沟通过
with others
和其他人一起
and put things in order
并把事情整理好
need
需要
Complete work report
完成工作报告
fully understand
完全了解
Mr. Chen
陈先生
this time
这次
it was an accident
这是一次意外
I know
我知道
I trust you
我相信你
but we must
但我们必须
we must pass
我们必须通过
mayor
市长
You must go and see
你一定要去看看
Xiaolu Museum
小鲁博物馆
very beautiful
很漂亮
Let's chat when we have time
有空的时候我们聊聊
i saw a girl
我看到一个女孩
It seems like this
好像是这样
The girl who plays games
那个玩游戏的女孩
In the U.S
在美国
Why is she in Tianhai?
她怎么会在天海？
I do not know yet
我还不知道
I'll find a chance to ask Teacher Lu
我找个机会问问卢老师
but
但
I think if
我想如果
Very enthusiastic
非常热情